On the block deal that took place in ICICI Lombard,
now a news is coming from CNBC TV18
that ICICI Bank, which is the
promoter entity, has bought it and
Bhartiya Enterprises, which had it till now, has
sold it and there is a good move here. At this
time, it is being considered a clean out trade.
Normally, stocks outperform after a clean out trade
and this is probably
happening here as well. Right now, ICICI Lombard
Manas, any view
on this, see the trend in ICICI GI is
definitely positive. This is a
breakout of a flag pattern, whose target is
around 1745. So I think
you can see an up move of 50% from the current level.
You can still buy at the current levels.
Place stop losses below 1669.
Okay, so right now, this is ICICI Lombard or
ICICI GI on this, woo. Now let's do one thing, let's
address today's Stocks of the Day
and go to Sumit first, but
before that, let's talk about Havells which is today.
Why did this move happen in Havells, which is the stock of the day? Sumit. Good morning. Today,
due to the Goldman Sachs report for Havells, a good up move is
seen. Coleman Sachs has
released a report and has upgraded Havells.
Along with the upgrade, the target seems to be
around ₹160.
They have
talked about multiple tailwinds. First, the
company is on the path of growth revival along with good leadership and
good distribution growth.
They feel that from here a good
upside will be seen opening up in the stock
because the recent cost cutting done by the company will provide
some support to the margins of the company
and they will
also be seen coming within the going forward numbers. Plus, due to
outsourcing in front of own manufacturing, there has been
some easing out in its costs, so that will also be good for the company. This
company is
continuously spending on its brands and new capacity.  The ad
is given below. Recently, she is also
working for the company in Rajasthan and
talks of double digit revenue growth are being done.
Also, in the last quarter's numbers,
very strong numbers of LDS came, so there is
a continuous improvement
seen on the margin front there too. In this context,
a buy report is being given on Havells
with a target of 1600 to 1660.
What are today's stocks of the day?
If we look at the remaining stocks apart from Havells, the first name that comes up
is Andhra Cement, where there are
talks of selling a part from some promoters and there are
talks of selling a part around 5. However, the initial impact on this stock
is negative around 4. The lower price is around 90,
which means that
this price was kept at a discount of around 19 to 20 from yesterday's closing.
An impact of this is being
seen here.  CMS Info where
a block happened around 28 in the
morning and that was a block of around 45 crore shares
and a block deal of around 16641 crores was
seen happening,
CNBC Awas had already mentioned and
now their news is confirmed here, earlier it was above 2
but now it is seen reaching the red mark
and Jari Agar where the
company has sold one of its land, the
impact of selling that land was there, a
rise of around 5 per cent is being seen in the stock here in the initial trading,
they have signed an agreement with Avari Infinity, there is
land worth around 80 crores which they are
selling in Goa and its impact is
visible in the stock, a
rise of around 5 per cent is being seen here,
thank you, thank you Sumit for this complete
information and please bring to the Jari screen once and let's
see its today's behavior, almost at 0 above 231
level, let's also tell its chart once
and yes 231  90 and you should
understand this level that at this time, in the
last five-
seven days, it almost revisited the
highs of all the sessions from February 19 till now.
After that, there was a slight sinking and on the
average Nifty was around 20 points higher.
But if you compare it with today's low, the 10-
day expo has maintained a fairly good
differential from that. Some PSUs are
moving. I had mentioned PNB, it is
moving a little. Bank of
Baroda is generating a little swing at this time.
Let's check what SBI is doing. SBI was
sinking in the morning but as of
now, if you look at SBI, it is around
761 p.e., yes, it is a good reaction. I mean, it is
traveling above yesterday's body. Here,
a small view of yours,
see here on SBI, consolidation is visible.
If you look at the last seven-eight sessions, there
is support on the stock at the lower level around 750. On the upward side, 775.  There
is resistance around 766 but if we talk about the undertone then
it is definitely bullish,
so if you have a long position then stay
in your position with a stop loss of 749,
however fresh buying advice will be
on breakout, if it crosses 766 then
buy there because in that the
stock can test the level of 800.